yipit.com 2018-04-09

# Privacy Policy | Yipit

Yipit cares about your privacy and takes it very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By signing up for the Yipit website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

#### What does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers Yipit's treatment of personal information that Yipit gathers when you are on the Yipit website and when you use Yipit services.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Yipit does not own or control, or to individuals that Yipit does not employ or manage.

#### What personal information about users does Yipit collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website.

Yipit may collect personally identifying information during the registration process, including name, email address, address, gender, store preferences etc. Yipit also may, on occasion collect user preference information (such as items clicked from emails). We may also store information users knowingly provide such as feedback forms, suggestions, and emails to the Yipit website. Yipit may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, email and web design optimizations, new features, and editorial and feedback purposes. Information entered may be aggregated across all users in order to determine and target demographics for marketing and advertising purposes.

All user information stored by Yipit is considered confidential and will not be shared with outside parties except as described herein. Yipit may share aggregated results of preferences for all users for marketing and advertising purposes.

If you object to such use for any reason, you can either let us know by sending us feedback, or you can unsubscribe from the Yipit email service.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Yipit will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

#### What about cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Yipit cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on many browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Yipit's most attractive features.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

#### Will Yipit share any of the information it receives?

Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We share your personal information only as described below.

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Yipit, our employees, our users, or others.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site, including through our emails. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) (visit <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/> if you reside in the United Kingdom) and Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

From time to time, we make our mailing list available to reputable companies whose products or services we believe will be of relevance to you and whose privacy practices meet the Direct Marketing Association's privacy standards. If you do not want to receive mailings, either electronically or physically, from other reputable companies, please contact us by email at help@yipit.com or by writing to us at our mailing address listed below.

We may share your information in connection with a merger between Yipit and another entity, or in the event of a transfer of all or some of our assets to another company.

#### Is information about me secure?

Your Yipit account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

#### Links to Other Sites

Yipit uses links to guide you toward valuable products, services and editorial. We are not responsible for any content that appears on these sites, nor do we endorse them. For questions about these sites, please consult their individual privacy policies.

#### Age Appropriate Content

Yipit is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to use the site, provide any personal information or receive our email distributions. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s)or legal guardian(s) before viewing the website or receiving emails.

#### How do I Unsubscribe?

To unsubscribe, click on the unsubscribe link in any Yipit email. You will be taken to a confirmation page. Click on the confirm link and you will be unsubscribed. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email to [unsubscribe@yipit.com](mailto:unsubscribe@yipit.com).

As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

#### Modifications to Privacy Policy

Yipit reserves the right to change this policy from time to time, however, all changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy at the time such changes are made. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page so please check back. Please note that continued access of Yipit will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of the Yipit Privacy Policy, please e-mail us. We welcome your questions and feedback. Please send all emails to: [terms@yipit.com](mailto:terms@yipit.com). Our corporate mailing address is Yipit, Inc., 22 West 19th Street, 7th Floor, New York, NY 10011.

Last modified: May 26, 2016.
